<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GPS Share</string><string name="acquiring_signal">Acquiring location</string>
    
    <string name="send_button">Send Location</string><string name="location_lost">Your location is momentarily unavailable.</string><string name="share_location_subject">My current location</string>
	
	<string name="share_location_body">Here is a link to my current location: </string>
	
	<string name="share_title">Share Location</string>
	<string name="no_way_to_share">No apps available to share location with</string>
	<string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_map_mode">Map Mode</string>
    <string name="menu_satellite_mode">Satellite Mode</string>
    <string name="menu_preferences">Settings</string><string name="about_title">About GPS Share</string>
    <string name="close_button">Close</string>
    <string name="about">Version 1.4.1&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;a href=&quot;http://kenkinder.com/gps-share/&quot;&gt;kenkinder.com/gps-share/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        Use GPS Share to share your location how you want, whether it\'s SMS,
        Email, Twitter, or something else. Because GPS Share uses no external
        services besides Google Maps, your privacy isn\'t a concern. GPS
        Share is an Open Source application and has no advertising. Internet
        access is used only to download Google Maps tiles.&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        Copyright © 2011 Ken Kinder&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
        of this software and associated documentation files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to deal
        in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
        to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
        copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
        furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
        all copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;br/&gt;
        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
        IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
        FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
        AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
        LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
        OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
        THE SOFTWARE.
    </string>
    <string name="preferences_activity">GPS Share Settings</string>
    <string name="message_subject_preference">Default Subject</string>
    <string name="message_subject_preference_summary">Subject for things like email</string>
    <string name="message_body_preference">Default Message Body</string>
    <string name="message_body_preference_summary">Text before the map link</string>
    <string name="menu_recenter">Recenter Map</string>
</resources>
